There was a boy I used to be
Who saw the world so simply
Thought every road was straight and true
Beneath the sky of perfect blue
He thought that love was just a phrase
For sunny easy golden days
He called you all his guiding stars Before he
knew
But I learned the sky can fall away and turn a
bright and sunny day to grey And in the static and
the night you were my only guiding light, more
than a feeling More than a name You were the fire,
you were the flame That led me through the
pouring rain And brought me back to life again
I learned to wear a painted smile
And walk a cold and lonely mile
To build a wall of industrial sound On cold and
unfamiliar ground
I learned how silence has a way
And how a heart can fill with hate
I learned that trust can be a lie Beneath a cold
and empty sky Two stars I hear held close and
tight One shines a warm and distant light A
friendly face on a glowing screen
The miles can't ever come between The bond we
made, the truth we know Helping a broken boy to
grow And when the sky would fall away And turn a
bright and sunny day to grey And in the static and
the night you were my only guiding light More
than a feeling, more than a name You were the
fire, you were the flame That led me through the
pouring rain And brought me back to life again
you
See you.